ILR School Ives Hallway Portrait Gallery Photographs /4280 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Ives Hallway Portrait Gallery Photographs
0000-2999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4280 P
0.67 cubic feet
0.7 linear ft.
Photographs.
This collection consists of portraits of many labor leaders and labor activists. These portraits hung on the hallway walls of Ives Hall, at the ILR School. For a complete listing see the folder listing for this collection.
7934128
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 20, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of portraits of many labor leaders and labor activists. These portraits hung on the hallway walls of Ives Hall, at the ILR School. For a complete listing see the folder listing for this collection.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6037 P: Labor Leaders and Subjects Photographs
Labor leaders -- Photographs; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
7934128
- Marcus Alonzo Hanna (1837-1904) Capitalist, Politician: Agnes Nestor (1880-1948) Labor Leader, Suffragette (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Matthew Woll (1880-1956) Pres. Int'l. Photo Engravers Union of N.A.: Iorwith Wilber Abel (1908-) Pres. United Steelworkers of America (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Andrew Furuseth (1854-1938) Pres. Int'l. Seamen's Union: William Dudley Haywood (1869-1928) Organizer (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Louis Dembitz Brandeis (1856-1941) Supreme Court Justice: Elbert Henry Gary (1864-1927) Corporation Lawyer Financier (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Mary Harris Jones (1830-1930) Labor Leader: John Llewellyn Lewis (1880-1969) Pres. United Mine Workers of America (Box 1, Folder 5)
- John Philip Frey (1871-1957) Vice Pres. Int'l. Molders and Foundry Workers of America: Walter Philip Reuther (1907-1970) Pres. United Automobile, Aircraft, Agricultural Implement Workers of America (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Eugene Victor Debs (1855-1926) Socialist Labor Organizer: William Sidell (1915-) General Pres. Bro. of Carpenters and Joiners of America (Box 1, Folder 7)
- David Dubinsky (1892-1982) Pres. ILGWU: Peter Joseph Brennan (1918-) Pres. Construction Trades Council of Greater NY (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Ethan Henry Gary (1846-1927) Corporation Lawyer Financier: Owen D. Young (1874-1962) Corporate Officer (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Samuel Gompers (1850-1924) Pres. AFL: David Lewis Behnke (1897-1953) Pres. Air Line Pilots Assoc. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- William Green (1872-1952) Pres. AFL: William Hugh Johnston (1874-1937) Pres. Int'l. Assoc. of Machinists (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Paul Joseph Jennings (1918-) Pres. Int'l. Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers: Oliver Wendal Holmes (1841-1935) Supreme Court Justice (Box 1, Folder 12)
- George Mortimer Pullman (1831-1897) Industrialist: Seth Low (1850-1916) Political Reformer (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Alfred Pritchard Sloan, Jr. (1875-1966) Industrialist: Norman Thomas (1884-1969) Socialist Leader (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Jay Gould (1836-1892) Financier: Ralph Montgomery Easley (1856-1939) Reformer (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Terence Vincent Powderly (1849-1924) Grandmaster Workman Knights of Labor: Horace Greely (1811-1872) Editor, Political Leader (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Charles Luna (1906-) First Pres. UTU: Elizabeth Gurley Flynn (1890-1964) Socialist, Labor Organizer (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Joseph Daniel Keenan (1896-) Int'l. Secretary IBEW: Hugo Lafayette Black (1886-) Supreme Court Justice (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Michael Joseph Quill (1905-1966) Pres. Transport Workers Union of America: Lincoln Steffens (1866-1936) Journalist, Reformer (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Al H. Chesser (1914-) Pres. UTU: Harriet Tubman (1821-1913) Abolitionist, Author (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Harold J. Gibbons (1910-) Vice Pres. Int'l. Bro. of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America: Clarence Seward Darrow (1857-1938) Social Reformer (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Henry Ford II (1917-) Automobile Manufacturer: Robert Alphonso Taft (1889-1953) U.S. Senator (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Charles Michael Schwab (1862-1939) Industrialist: Hubert Horatio Humphrey (1911-1978) United States Senator Labor and Civil Rights Advocate (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Henry Ford I (1863-1947) Automobile Manufacturer: Emma Goldman (1869-1940) Social Reformer (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Edsel Ford (1893-1943) Automobile Manufacturer: Harry VanArsdale, Jr. (1905-) Pres. NYC Central Labor Council (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Frank Edward Fitzsimmons (1908-) Pres. Int'l. Bro. of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America: David John McDonald (1902-) Pres. United Steelworkers of America (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Delores Clara Huerta (1930-) First Vice-Pres. United Farm Workers of America (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Margaret Drier Robins (1869-1945) Social Economist (Box 1, Folder 28)
- A. Philip Randolph (1889-) Pres. Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters (Box 1, Folder 29)